(Penny:)-Well, that's not gonna happen.
-I assumed that.
(Sheldon:)-Hence my true purpose in coming here.
-Which is?
(Sheldon:)I want you to crawl back to him
and apologize.
(Penny:)-I'm busy.
-Excuse me, miss. I'd like to order lunch.
(Penny:)-Fine. What do you want?
-I have a few questions.
(Sheldon:)First, I notice that you offer
soup and a half sandwich.
(Penny:)-Yes.
-Where exactly...
(Sheldon:)...does the half-sandwich come from?
(Sheldon:)Are you giving me half
of someone else's sandwich?
(Sheldon:)Or do I have to wait for someone else
to order the other half?
(Penny:)No. Sheldon, they just make
a half sandwich.
You can't make a half sandwich.
(Sheldon:)If it's not half of a whole sandwich,
it's just a small sandwich.
(Penny:)Okay, fine.
It's soup and a small sandwich.
(Penny:)-Is that what you want?
-Of course not. I'll have my usual.
(Sheldon:)-Great.
-Aren't you gonna ask...
(Sheldon:)-...if I want a beverage?
-Usually lemonade?
(Penny:)-Yes.
-Want lemonade?
-Anything else?
(Sheldon:)Yes. I want you to apologize to Leonard.
(Penny:)I am not going to apologize.
I've done nothing. He's overreacting.